var questions = [
    {
        question: "The casting team originally wanted who to audition for the role of Dwight?",
        choices: ["John Krasinski", "Steve Carell", "Rainn Wilson", "Will Ferrell"],
        answer: "John Krasinski"
    },
    {
        question: "During his embarrassing Dundie award presentation, who is Michael Scott presenting a Dundie award when he sings along to 'You Sexy Thing' by ’70s British funk band Hot Chocolate??",
        choices: ["Jim", "Ryan", "Danny", "Roy"],
        answer: "Ryan"
    },
    {
        question: "In 'The Alliance' episode, Michael is asked by Oscar to donate to his nephew’s walkathon for a charity. How much money does Michael donate, not realizing that the donation is per mile and not a flat amount?",
        choices: ["$15", "$20", "$25", "$30"],
        answer: "$25"
    },
    {
        question: "What county in Pennsylvania is the Dunder Mifflin Scranton branch located in?",
        choices: ["Lancaster County", "Lawrence County", "Luzerne County", "Lackawanna County"],
        answer: "Lackawanna County"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the exclusive club that Pam, Oscar, and Toby Flenderson establish in the episode 'Branch Wars'?",
        choices: ["Finer Things Club", "Dunder Mifflin Executives", "Dunder Mifflinfinity", "DM Book Club"],
        answer: "Finer Things Club"
    },
    {
        question: "What substance does Jim put office supplies owned by Dwight into?",
        choices: ["Whipped Cream", "Jello", "Cement", "Glue"],
        answer: "Jello"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the employee who started as 'the temp' in the Dunder Mifflin office?",
        choices: ["Jim", "Dwight", "Ryan", "Creed"],
        answer: "Ryan"
    },
    {
        question: "Rainn Wilson did not originally audition for the iconic beet farming Dwight Schrute; instead, he auditioned for which part?",
        choices: ["Jim Halpert", "Creed Bratton", "Stanley Hudson", "Michael Scott"],
        answer: "Michael Scott"
    },
    {
        question: "Dwight owns and runs a farm in his spare time. What does this farm primarily produce?",
        choices: ["Beets", "Asparagus", "Corn", "Chick Peas"],
        answer: "Beets"
    },
    {
        question: "In the 'Diversity Day' episode, what famous comedian’s stand up routine does Michael imitate?",
        choices: ["Dave Chappelle", "Chris Rock", "Richard Pryor", "Eddie Murphy"],
        answer: "Chris Rock"
    },
    {
        question: "In the episode 'The Client,' the employees read Michael’s movie script. Which employee read the part of Goldenface?",
        choices: ["Jim", "Dwight", "Oscar", "Ryan"],
        answer: "Oscar"
    },
    {
        question: "What stolen item does Michael pretend to fire Pam over in season one?",
        choices: ["Staples", "Pens", "Paper", "Post-Its"],
        answer: "Post-Its"
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of sandwich does Michael have a dream about when he’s the head of Michael Scott Paper Company?",
        choices: ["PB and tuna", "PB and Bananas", "PB and Carrots", "PB and Steak"],
        answer: "PB and tuna"
    },
    {
        question: "What’s the name of Dwight’s porcupine?",
        choices: ["Henry", "Henrietta", "Harry", "Hannah"],
        answer: "Henrietta"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Jim use to make Dwight salivate in 'Phyllis’ Wedding'?",
        choices: ["Mentos", "Peppermints", "Altoids", "Certs"],
        answer: "Altoids"
    },
    {
        question: "What of the following colors does Angela think is 'whore-ish'?",
        choices: ["Red", "Blue", "Yellow", "Green"],
        answer: "Green"
    },
    {
        question: "Jim Halpert knows the flavor of yogurt that Pam likes best, what is it?",
        choices: ["Mixed Berry", "Strawberry", "Vanilla", "Blueberry"],
        answer: "Mixed Berry"
    },
    {
        question: "Who took over Pam as the receptionist after she went to art school in season 5?",
        choices: ["Randine", "Ronni", "Rachel", "Rose"],
        answer: "Ronni"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Toby’s daughter’s name?",
        choices: ["Sarah", "Sally", "Sasha", "Sophie"],
        answer: "Sasha"
    },
    {
        question: "Who punches a hole in the wall between Michael’s office and the conference room?",
        choices: ["Jim", "Ryan", "Packer", "Andy"],
        answer: "Andy"
    },
    {
        question: "In the Season 4 pilot episode 'Fun Run,' what cause does Michael organize a fun run for?",
        choices: ["Rabies", "AIDS", "Science", "Bat Birth Control"],
        answer: "Rabies"
    },
    {
        question: "What color does Dwight paint Michael’s office when he thinks he’s taking over Michael’s job?",
        choices: ["Blue", "Black", "Red", "Orange"],
        answer: "Black"
    },
    {
        question: "Which network produced 'The Office'?",
        choices: ["ABC", "FOX", "NBC", "CBS"],
        answer: "NBC"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of Angela’s cats does Dwight freeze?",
        choices: ["Sparkles", "Miss Lady", "Bandit", "Sprinkles"],
        answer: "Sprinkles"
    },
    {
        question: "Which cast member was having an affair with Angela’s fiancé, the senator?",
        choices: ["Oscar", "Andy", "Dwight", "Stanley"],
        answer: "Oscar"
    },
    {
        question: "Which office employee did Michael hit with his car?",
        choices: ["Creed", "Meredith", "Kelly", "Toby"],
        answer: "Meredith"
    },
    {
        question: "Who started the fire?",
        choices: ["Dwight", "Darryl", "Ryan", "Michael"],
        answer: "Ryan"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Michael’s username for the online dating website?",
        choices: ["2 Hot 4 U", "Date Mike", "WLLHNG", "Little Kid Lover"],
        answer: "Little Kid Lover"
    },
    {
        question: "What vegetable does Michael force-feed Kevin?",
        choices: ["Broccoli", "Brussel Sprouts", "Carrots", "Peas"],
        answer: "Broccoli"
    },
    {
        question: "Whose mother does Michael date?",
        choices: ["Jim", "Pam", "Ryan", "Kevin"],
        answer: "Pam"
    },
    {
        question: "Who convinces Dwight that the CIA is recruiting him?",
        choices: ["Jim", "Michael", "Pam", "Mose"],
        answer: "Pam"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Kevin’s cover band?",
        choices: ["Scrantonicity", "Kevin and the Zits", "Mouse Rat", "Scrantonicity 2"],
        answer: "Scrantonicity 2"
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Jim propose to Pam?",
        choices: ["Gas station", "The Office", "Pratt Institue", "New York City"],
        answer: "Gas station"
    },
    {
        question: "In the episode 'Basketball,' who does Michael say is on the team, ‘of course’?",
        choices: ["Darryl", "Stanley", "Ryan", "Phyllis"],
        answer: "Stanley"
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Michael get his 'World’s Best Boss' mug?",
        choices: ["Wal-Mart", "Sky Mall", "Spencer Gifts", "Sharper Image"],
        answer: "Spencer Gifts"
    },
    {
        question: "In the 'St. Patrick’s Day' episode, who gets sick on their first date with Andy?",
        choices: ["Angela", "Jessica", "Jamie", "Erin"],
        answer: "Erin"
    },
    {
        question: "Who wins the Fun Run in season 4?",
        choices: ["Toby", "Dwight", "Jim", "Michael"],
        answer: "Toby"
    },
    {
        question: "What actor on The Office shot the opening credit footage?",
        choices: ["B.J. Novak", "John Krasinski", "Rainn Wilson", "Creed Bratton"],
        answer: "John Krasinski"
    },
    {
        question: "What item of clothing does Michael insist on having dry cleaned?",
        choices: ["His socks", "His shirts", "His jeans", "His underwear"],
        answer: "His jeans"
    },
    {
        question: "Who wins the bronze medal in the episode, “Office Olympics”?",
        choices: ["Michael", "Dwight", "Kevin", "Jim"],
        answer: "Jim"
    },
    {
        question: "In the episode “Diwali,” who attempts to kiss Pam?",
        choices: ["Michael", "Toby", "Roy", "Jim"],
        answer: "Michael"
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of Michael’s girlfriends in The Office was played by Steve Carell’s real-life wife?",
        choices: ["Jan", "Carol", "Holly", "Donna"],
        answer: "Carol"
    },
    {
        question: "What can Dwight Shrute supposedly raise and lower at his will?",
        choices: ["His blood pressure", "His heart rate", "His cholesterol", "His temperature"],
        answer: "His cholesterol"
    },
    {
        question: "What movie does Michael say that Dwight cried during?",
        choices: ["Apollo 13", "Independence Day", "Deep Impact", "Armageddon"],
        answer: "Armageddon"
    },
    {
        question: "When is Michael’s birthday?",
        choices: ["March 15", "May 23", "August 4", "November 30"],
        answer: "March 15"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was sent to anger management?",
        choices: ["Dwight", "Andy", "Packer", "Darryl"],
        answer: "Andy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the annual employee awards night on the show?",
        choices: ["Mifflies", "Scott's Awards", "Dundies", "Mikies"],
        answer: "Dundies"
    },
    {
        question: "In the episode 'Goodbye Michael,' what does Pam say Michael seems full of at the end of the episode?",
        choices: ["Wonder", "Excitement", "Fear", "Hope"],
        answer: "Hope"
    },
    {
        question: "In the episode 'Chair Model,' Pam would receive Michael’s chair when he got a new one. Who would get Pam’s chair?",
        choices: ["Creed", "Andy", "Jim", "Oscar"],
        answer: "Creed"
    },
    {
        question: "After the Fun Run to beat Rabies, who is the oversized check made out?",
        choices: ["Rabies", "Science", "Nurses", "Doctors"],
        answer: "Science"
    },
    {
        question: "Based on where he eats most often, what is Michael Scott’s favorite restaurant?",
        choices: ["Outback Steakhouse", "Applebees", "Chili’s", "Perkins"],
        answer: "Chili’s"
    },
    {
        question: "What art school did Pam go to?",
        choices: ["Art Institute", "New York University", "Lackawanna Community College", "Pratt Institute"],
        answer: "Pratt Institute"
    }
]


// Add time left after
// change main div attributes to css
// on site load go directly to first function
// put remove child next to each other

